{
    "subject": "resource/A_Lowland_Cinderella",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "United Kingdom",
    "human_readable": "A Lowland Cinderella is from the United Kingdom.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8881666660308838,
            "question": "Where is A Lowland Cinderella from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8809312582015991,
            "question": "Why do you think A Lowland Cinderella is set in the United Kingdom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7786293625831604,
            "question": "What country is A Lowland Cinderella associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6642363667488098,
            "question": "Is A Lowland Cinderella a fictional character?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6017813682556152,
            "question": "What kind of story is A Lowland Cinderella?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5322996377944946,
            "question": "Who might have created the story of A Lowland Cinderella?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5208502411842346,
            "question": "Is A Lowland Cinderella a popular fairytale?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4714292287826538,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about A Lowland Cinderella?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41565048694610596,
            "question": "Are there any other stories similar to A Lowland Cinderella?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17202353477478027,
            "question": "What are some common themes in fairytales from the United Kingdom?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=A Lowland Cinderella is from the United Kingdom.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4719_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other stories similar to A Lowland Cinderella?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4719_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about A Lowland Cinderella?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4719_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is A Lowland Cinderella a popular fairytale?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4719_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4719_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4719_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4719_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4719_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4719_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4719_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4719_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4719_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4719_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4719_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that \"A Lowland Cinderella\" is associated with the United Kingdom, specifically mentioning its production by the Progress Film Company and filming locations such as Shoreham and Brighton, both in the UK."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}